Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/marisa-k-a2a2463a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare

Nursing

Regulatory Compliance

Certifications

CNOR

BLS

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Marisa Kuhns

MBA Candidate BSN, RN, CNOR

Houston, Texas

Summary

I am an experienced Registered Nurse with an eye for efficiency and attention to detail. I embrace change as an avenue towards improvement and enjoy disseminating the latest in evidence based practice. Learning in a fast paced environment and communicating effectively on interdisciplinary teams are skills I have honed in many diverse environments.

Experience

CHI St. Luke's Health
Regulatory Compliance RN
March 2018 - Present (2 years 3 months)

Franciscan St. Francis Health Registered Nurse 2012 - December 2018 (6 years)

Cardiothoracic and Vascular Operating Room & Hybrid Circulating and Scrub RN

Nursing Research Committee

NursesRx Travel Registered Nurse 2013 - 2018 (5 years)

Various locations

Baylor St. Luke's Medical Center- Houston, TX

Heart Hospital of Austin- Austin,

TX

University of Chicago- Chicago, IL

Clear Lake Regional Medical Center- Webster, TX

Memorial Hermann Heart and Vascular Institute- Houston, TX

Mercy General Hospital-Sacramento, CA

Baptist Medical Center- San Antonio, TX

Cape Fear Valley Medical Center- Fayetteville, NC

St. Vincent Heart Center of Indiana Registered Nurse 2009 - 2012 (3 years)

Indianapolis, Indiana Area

Cardiothoracic and Vascular Operating Room & Hybrid Circulating RN Cardiac Progressive Critical Care Registered Nurse

- Quality Best Practice Committee
- Shared Governance Committee

Education

Valparaiso University

Bachelor of Science in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse